OYELAKIN TAYO DAMOLA

DATA ENTRY ASSISTANT

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Data management with more than four years of experience in verifying complex data, database maintenance and producing daily, weekly and monthly reports using advanced Excel functions such as vlookup, basic knowledge of SQL, Power BI and other data analyst tools, Excellent time management and multitasking abilities. I am an enthusiastic, selfmotivated, reliable, responsible and hard working person.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Entry Assistant, 2020 till Date

APIN Public Health Initiatives [APIN]

No 1, Plot 8b Ondo Close, off Oshuntokun Avenue Old Bodija. Oyo State.

- Assisting HI Team in data cleaning and ensure data accuracy Ensure completion of patient's data record from registration point and updating patient's health records using OpenMRS.
- Ensure Data integrity and confidentiality
- Assisting Focal person to track Lost-to-Followup [LTFU] with Excel Linelist.
- Ensure concurrency of data between Database [EMR] and National Data Repository [NDR] with help VLOOKUP Excel Function.
- Regularly checking patients' record to know when due for drugs pickup and viral load bleeding.

Lead Data Manager, 2019-2020

Center for Integrated Health Programs (CHIP)

Lagos State University Teaching Hospital, Ikeja Lagos.

- Ensure all patients information daily get capture by used all relevant registers.
- Ensure all patients' pharmacy forms get captured.
- Generating daily Backups and XML Files.
- checked all register and forms for data completeness
- Enrolled and captured all Patients for Patient Biometric System [PBS]
- Generate daily and weekly report

Part-Time Lecturer, 2018-2019

The Polytechnic Ibadan Department of Logistic and Transport (Poly Consult), Ibadan Oyo.

- Prepared lecture guides for the class before lecture schedule period.
- Used Visual displayed diagram for more illustration in the class.
- Assessed the students through class assignment and test.
- Take attendant in the class and avoid late to class.

CONTACT

Address: No. 29, Zone 5 Orisunmibare Ogbere Kehinsi Ibadan,

Email: oyelakintayodamola@gmail.com

Oyo State, Nigeria.

Phone: 08062197769

SKILLS

- Data cleaning and preparation
- Data analysis and exploration
- Statistical knowledge
- Creating data visualizations
- Creating dashboards and reports
- Writing and communication
- Problem solving
- Spreadsheet
- **Basic SQL**
- **Data Collection**
- Information Verification
- Googling with Google Searching **Engine**
- **Graphic Design**

• Oyo Data Management Teams' Reviews Meetings 27 July 2022

Organizer: APIN

Oyo Data Management Teams' Reviews Meetings 1st June 2022

Organizer: APIN

Accelerated Jobberman Soft Skill Training with Certificate 10th October 2021

Organizer: Jobberman Online

- Oyo Data Management Teams' Reviews Meetings 16 March 2021 **Organizer: APIN**
- Gender-Based Violence Service Assessment and Mapping Agenda for Data Collectors' Training 9th-12th November 2020

Organizer: JHPIEGO

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

National Youth Service Corps

Directorate Headquarters Plot 416, Tigris Crescent, Off Aguiyi Ironsi Street, Maitama, P.M.B 138 Abuja

Bachelor of Science: Transport Management

Ladoke Akintola University of Technology Ogbomoso, Oyo State.

2019

2012-2018

International Diploma in Logistics and Transport The Chartered Institute of Logistics and Transport International Incorporated by Royal Charter 1926 United Kingdom	2013
Professional Diploma in Logistics and Transport Management. The Polytechnic, Ibadan Oyo State.	2008-2010
Certificate Course in Computer Operations with Merit The Polytechnic, Ibadan Oyo State.	2010
SSCE Certificate. Oke 'Badan High School Oluyoro Oke Offa Ibadan.	1996-2002
Testimonial Certificate. Community Primary School Ogbere Oloba Ibadan	1989-1995

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS		
Introduction To Structure Simplifearn Online Training		04 th July 2022
Introduction to Data Analy IBM & Cousera Online Class	•	June 24, 2022
Declaration of Completion Simplification Online Training	-	20 th June 2022
Declaration of Completion Simplificarn Online Training	_	11 th June 2022
Certificate of Completion Ifective Online Training	in Data Analytics Using MS Exce	1 21 st May 2022
Declaration of Completion Simplification Online Training	n in Business Analytics with Exce	l 12 th May 2022
Certificate of Completion Earn and Excel by Sohail A		29 st Sept. 2021